Lewis Mason 07909441886

lewisjmason@hotmail.com

14 Frogmoor Avenue Oakenshaw Bradford BD12 7AF

#### **Profile**

Confident and adaptable, having built up experience in Retail, Merchandising and Sales over the past 10 years I'm looking for a challenge to help me put my skills into practice and develop them further.

"I would whole heartedly recommend Lewis due to his ability, attitude and work ethic." Neil Foster, Planning Manager at BEL Valves Ltd (Ref. LinkedIn Recommendations)

#### **Experience**

## Brand Ambassador at SIG iTeam (Apple & iTunes Client)

2015-Present

Representing the biggest technology company in the world, I am responsible for the merchandising and maintenance of Apple hardware and software throughout various retailers across the UK. Collaborating closely with Dixons Store Group, John Lewis & Partners and multiple telecoms companies.

Sporadically overlooking the North Team (11 BAs) due to managers absence, as acting National Account Manager I create and deliver numerous data heavy reports to clients as well as managing the teams call compliance.

I have executed the installation of Apple hardware including; Apple Watch, iPad and iPhone. I have recently completed the 2019 launch of iPad Air & iMac, ensuring the UK was the first country to complete all retailers.

To guarantee product launches run smoothly, I direct numerous training sessions with tactical teams, mentoring them and building their knowledge so they themselves can complete this highly technical work.

Working with iTunes I negotiate space across the majority of retailers who sell iTunes Gift Cards, to increase sales and drive customers. I create weekly compliance reports about the work carried out across the UK, this information is shared directly with iTunes California who can then action new promotions in our stores.

## Store Supervisor at Jack Wills, Halifax

2013-2015

Stepping into a management role, I was responsible for supervising staff, creating daily financials and ensuring the store hit its sales targets. Achieving a BSc in IT Management at university, I was also the stores point of contact for all IT and maintenance issues, fixing devices from the tills on the shop floor to fixing network issues at the back end. With the introduction of JW Academy, I became a coach for 4 members of staff, ensuring they were competent and confident in their roles, teaching them the companies values and motivating them to reach their potentials.

# Sales/Operational Director, Hatmosphere, Newcastle

2012-2013

Co-founded a clothing company with 5 other business minded individuals. Focusing on sales strategies, event management and risk assessment, I contributed in setting up a small business and whilst learning on the job, made a small profit.

## IT Technician, BEL Valves, Newcastle

2011-2012

During my placement year at Northumbria University, I worked on designing and creating different methods for building valves. This included working with VBA and Excel. I created my own drawings that engineers continue to use daily to configure different valves.

#### **Education**

## **Northumbria University, Newcastle**

2009-2013

BSc Hons (MBCS) 2.1

IT Management for Business. 4 Year course including a placement year.

During my time at university I developed many skills, worked on varying projects and even learnt a foreign language. I developed a bespoke e-commerce website for a very talented jewellery designer, I learnt the fundamentals of PRINCE2 and SixSigma and co-founded a successful student run clothing company.

## **Brighouse Sixth Form, Brighouse**

2007-2009

3 A-Levels

Sociology (C), ICT (D), General Studies (D)

Picked up Business Studies as an additional AS Level during final year

## **Skills**

Proficient in Microsoft Office Programs Knowledge in various developer programs (VBA / SQL) Understanding of PRINCE2 Project Management Hands on Experience with Apple iOS and MacOS

### **Foreign Languages:**

Spanish - Beginner Level

## **References**

On Request